Yay!
イエーイ!
Did you have fun?
楽しかったですか?
It was fun.
楽しかったです
Please turn your hands.
手を回してください
Have you ever heard of that?
あれ、通常聞いたことあるの?
Yeah, but I might not remember it all that well.
ええ、でもあんま覚えてないかも
I might not remember much.
あんま覚えてないかも
That light.
そっちのライト
Yeah, hey.
うん、ねえ
So, where should we go first?
じゃあさあ、まずどこ行く?
Eh, what should I do?
えー、どうしよう
I want to eat salmon.
サーモン食べたい
Are you hungry?
お腹空いた?
I'm hungry.
お腹空いた
Do you eat salmon?
サーモン食べる?
Yeah.
うん
So where are you going?
じゃあどこ行くの?
Shop server sopper?
お店サーバーソッパー?
Yes, that's right.
うん、そうだね
Salmon?
サーモン?
Yeah yeah yeah.
うんうんうん
Is it okay to just use salmon?
サーモンだけでいいの?
Well, maybe not.
えー、ないかも
Yeah.
うん
Okay.
オッケー
Well, in order, it's probably salmon.
じゃあ順番的に多分サーモンとかだから
Yeah yeah.
うん うん
But let's look for it.
でも探そう
Hey, let's look for it.
ね、探そう
Sorry, I'm not wearing sushi for some reason.
ごめんね、なんかちょっとお寿司履いてなくて
Yeah, not at all.
うん、全然全然
It turned out like this.
こんななんかとなっちゃったけど
Are you okay.
大丈夫
Are you okay?
大丈夫?
Yeah.
うん
thank you.
ありがとう
So just choose the menu?
じゃあただメニュー選ぶ?
Yeah, let's choose.
うん、選ぼう
I wonder if it's salmon.
あるかな、サーモン
Well, I want to eat salmon.
えー、サーモン食べたいんだよね
Oh, it seems like that.
あ、なんかね、あれらしいよ
It seems to be selected using this touch panel.
このタッチパネルで選ぶらしい
It's kind of amazing.
なんか、すごいね
Oh, really, it's kind of stylish.
あ、ほんとだ、なんかお洒落ね
Right?
でしょ?
Isn't there?
ないの?
Is there no hokkai?
ほっかいのないの?
this system.
このシステム
Eh,
えー、
We were always playing ping pong.
ピ ンポンいつもしてた
Oh, really?
あ、そう?
Yeah.
うん
There was salmon.
サーモンあった
there were?
あった?
Seriously?
マジ?
So please, please?
じゃあ頼む頼む?
ask.
頼む
Eat what you like.
好きなもの食べよ
nice.
いいね
Hmm.
う ーん
Two.
2つ
Yeah.
うん
Well then, I'll order some food and drinks.
じゃあ食べ物とさ、飲み物頼むとさ、
Let's talk this far.
ここまで喋ろうよ
I was able to do it.
できた
Did you do it?
できた?
Yeah.
うん
Looks delicious.
おいしそう
おいしそうだね
Also, what kind of salmon did you order?
あとサーモンとか何注文したの?
that.
それ
Basashi.
バサシ
Ah, Basashi?
あ、バサシ?
Do you like Basashi?
バサシ好きなの?
challenge?
挑戦?
Yes, a challenge.
うん、挑戦
Oh, nice.
おー、いいね
Well then, let's have a toast.
じゃあ、乾杯する
Cheers.
乾杯ー
delicious?
おいしい?
delicious.
おいしい
Are you glad it wasn't alcohol?
お酒じゃなくてよかったの?
Yeah.
うん
Yeah, yeah, yeah, no?
そう、そう、そう、ダメなの?
Yeah, that's right.
うん、そうなの
Shall we eat then?
じゃあ食べる?
Yeah.
うん
Shall we eat?
食べよっか
It's okay to eat.
食べていいや
I'll take it.
いただきまーす
soy sauce.
醤油
Ah, soy sauce.
あ、醤油
How old is the salmon?
サーモンいつぶり?
Yeah.
うん
Ahahahaha.
あはははは
Eating a drink.
飲み物食べてる
You're eating.
食べてるね
Oh, you don't like sushi?
あ、お寿司苦手なの?
Yeah.
うん
It's cute.
可愛いね
As expected.
さすが
It's still a big deal.
まだまだおごちさまだね
delicious?
おいしい?
Ah, good.
あ はは、よかった
Good, I'm glad you're here.
よかった、ここ来てよかったね
Yeah.
うん
Goo, goo.
グ ー、グー
Yeah.
うん
delicious.
おいしい
Well then, let me eat too.
じゃあさ、俺にも食べさせてよ
Add wasabi.
わさびつけよ
Should I put it on?
つけよっかな
Put it on.
つけよ
Just a little bit.
ちょっとだけ
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
うん、うん、うん
Yes, put wasabi on the salmon.
そう、わさびをサーモンにつけて
There are quite a lot.
結構多いぞ
This is quite a large amount.
結構、結構量多いぞこれ
from now.
これから
Thank you for waiting.
待って、ありがとうございます
Add soy sauce.
つけて、お醤油
Soy sauce.
お醤油
Yeah, yeah.
うん、 うん
Delicious, delicious, but a little wasabi.
おいしい、おいしいけどわさびはちょっと
Ah, it's delicious.
あ、おいしい
Looks delicious.
おいしそう
Hey, but it's delicious.
おい、でもおいしい
But it's delicious.
でもおいしいね
I did my best.
頑張った
So, are you going to university this year?
さ あ、あれ今年から大学?
Yes, that's right.
そう、そうだろ
Right?
でしょ?
Hey, did you pass?
ね、受かった?
I passed.
受かった
Where did you get accepted?
どこ受かったの?
It's tea.
お茶じゃん
You did your best.
頑張ったじゃん
I did my best.
頑 張った
But which school did you get accepted to?
でも、どこの学校受かったの?
I haven't been accepted.
受かってないよ
It seems kind of difficult.
なんか難しそう
That's right.
そう なんだ
What language do you study?
何の言語を勉強するの?
English.
英語
English?
英語?
It's kind of difficult, isn't it?
なんか難しいよね
It's English, isn't it?
英語だよね
What language are you studying?
何の言語を勉強してるの?
Boy, we were talking about studying abroad and things like that.
少年、留学したりとか、海外で話してた
Ah, it's solid.
あ、しっかりしてるね
Are you really 18 years old?
本当に18歳?
Yeah.
うん
That's too firm, isn't it?
しっかりしすぎでしょ
I didn't think anything of it when I was 18.
俺、18の時何も考えてなかったよ
No, I like it.
いや、いいね
I'm looking forward to it.
楽しみだね
University life.
大学生活
My dreams are expanding.
夢、膨らむね
Is there a club you'd like to join?
なんかさ、入ってみたいサークルとかあるの?
What I want to do when I go to university.
大学に行ってやってみたいこと
What is there?
何があるんだろう?
surely.
確かに
Don't you understand?
分かんないか
There's something about dance, and there's also a manga graduate school.
ダンス系とかさ、なんか漫画研究科とかあるじゃん
Please read the cultural festival.
文化祭読んでね
Yeah.
うん
Well then, why don't you give it a try?
じゃあちょっとさ、バサシ挑戦してみる?
It's like an encounter with Niche.
ニッチとの遭遇みたいな
So, add soy sauce.
それで、醤油をつけて
Even just a little bit is fine.
ちょっとでもいいよ
Just a bite is fine.
かじるぐらいでもいいよ
It's delicious.
美味しいよね
It's delicious, isn't it?
美味しいでしょ
cute.
可愛い
Come closer, you can come closer.
寄って、近寄っていいよ
It was delicious.
美味しかったね
Well then, shall we go eat something sweet?
じゃあさ、甘いもの食べに行く?
Yeah, let's go eat.
うん、食べに行こう
What do you eat?
何食べる?
Like Crake?
クレークとか?
I want to eat ice cream.
アイス食べたい
Ice cream?
アイスか
Okay.
いいよ
Shall we go eat ice cream?
アイス食べに行くか
Is there any?
あるかな?
What flavor do you like?
何味が好き?
Hmm, I like the refreshing style.
んー、さっぱり系が好き
Refreshing type and what type?
さっぱり系と何系?
Like lemon?
レモンとか?
Yeah, something like that.
うん、とか
I see.
なるほどね
Is there ice cream?
アイスあるかな?
It's cute.
可愛いね
Looks good on ice cream.
アイス似合いそう
Yeah, try your best not to look too cool.
うん、格好良さないように頑張って
Oh, there's ice cream.
あ、アイスあるじゃん
It's true.
本当だ
So, choose, choose.
じゃあ、選ぶ選ぶ
There's ice cream.
アイスあるじゃん
Which one would you choose?
どっちにする?
It's okay because I like it.
好きなのでいいよ
That's troubling.
悩ましいね
Both are colorful.
どっちもカラフル
Should I do it this way?
こっちにする?
Shall we eat?
食べよっか
delicious.
美味しい
delicious?
美味しい?
There are trees and it looks like a squirrel.
木もあってリスみたいだね
Looks like a small animal.
小動物みたい
delicious.
美味しい
What flavor is it?
何味だろう?
It feels like cotton candy.
わたあめみたいな感じ
Cotton candy?
わたあめ?
sweet?
甘い?
Don't you feel refreshed?
さっぱりしてない?
surely.
確かに
So, where should we go after eating ice cream?
じゃあ、アイス食べたどこ行く?
Don’t have a place you want to go?
行きたいところがない?
There's no place to put it.
入れるところがない
Will you say that?
そんなこと言ってくれるの?
Will you say such happy things?
こんな嬉しいこと言ってくれるの?
Is there no place for two people?
2人で入れるところがない?
So, let's go somewhere where the two of us can hang out while eating ice cream.
じゃあ、アイス食べながら2人一気になるところ行く?
The two of us are finally together.
やっと2人一気になったね
hey.
ね
happy.
嬉しい
It's cute.
可愛いね
Can I come closer?
もっと近づいていい?
It's close.
近いよ
how was it?
どう だった?
Date today.
今日デート
it was fun.
楽しかった
Was the salmon delicious?
サーモン美味しかった?
It was delicious.
美味しかった
Because you came all the way to see me,
せっかく会いに来てくれたからさ、
I want to go to more places tomorrow and the day after tomorrow.
もっと色んなところさ、明日と明後日行きたいんだけど
Where do you want to go next?
次どこ行きたい?
I want to go to Sky Tree.
スカイツリー行きたい
nice.
いいね
Want to see the night view?
夜景見たい?
I want to see it.
見たい
What do you think of this room?
この部屋どう?
That's amazing.
すごいね
It's so beautiful.
めちゃくちゃ綺麗
You worked a little hard.
ちょっと頑張りましたね
happy.
嬉しい
But, what about the Sky Tree?
でも さ、スカイツリーもなんだけど、
This room also has quite a night view.
この部屋も結構夜景があるんだよ
That's amazing.
すごいね
It doesn't show up on camera though.
カメラには映らないけど
It's true.
本当だ
Can you see Skye?
スカイが見えるかな?
Can you see it?
見えるかな?
I wonder what it is?
どうなんだろう?
Maybe I'll see it soon.
近 くで見るかもね
It's beautiful.
綺麗だね
Isn't it beautiful?
綺麗でしょ?
I tried my best.
ちょっと頑張りました
thank you.
ありがとうございます
Take a night view.
夜景撮って
Are you going over there?
あっち行く?
Huh?
あれ?
Isn't that the Sky Tree?
スカイツリーじゃない?
Is that so?
そうなのかな?
That's probably Sky Tree.
あれ多分スカイツリーだよ
It's beautiful.
綺麗だね
Are you going there tomorrow?
明日はそこ行くか?
I think I can go there.
そこ行けそう
It's close, right?
近いでしょ?
It's cute.
かわいいね
Let's be tighter.
もっとぎゅっとしよう
It smells good.
いい匂いする
Did you change the stars?
恒星変えた?
I don't know.
わかんない
Maybe it was changed.
変えたのかも
Does it smell good?
いい匂い?
shampoo?
シャンプー?
It's cute.
かわいいね
It smells good.
いい匂いする
it was good.
良かった
It's close.
近いね
Can I do that?
していい?
Can I chew it?
チューしていいの?
Yeah.
うん
Isn't it early?
早くない?
Are you okay?
大丈夫?
That's crazy, isn't it?
ヤバいよね
Is it dangerous?
ヤバい?
I'm also embarrassed.
俺も照れてる
Let's sit here.
ここ座ろう
Let's sit down.
座ろう
Can I have a bite now?
今、チューしちゃってもいい?
It's embarrassing.
恥ずかしいね
Are you embarrassed?
恥 ずかしい?
Well, let's use our memories.
じゃあ、思い出使おう
Yeah.
うん
How long can you hold your breath?
どういう間にさ、息我慢できるの?
I don't know.
わかんない
painful?
苦しい?
thank you.
ありがとう
It's a little close.
ちょっと近いなぁ
Is it a bit close?
ちょっと近い?
Should I come closer?
もっと近寄るか、じゃあ
Isn't it hot?
熱くない?
this.
これ
It might be hot.
熱いかも
No?
だめ?
Okay.
いいよ
Are you embarrassed?
恥ずかしい?
cute.
かわいい
Can I see it?
見ていい?
good
いい
Yo.
よ
Is it bad to be close?
近 いのはダメ?
It's embarrassing to be so close.
近いのは恥ずかしい
Is it embarrassing to be so close?
近いのは恥ずかしい?
It tickled me.
くすぐったの
Is the tickling weak?
くすぐったの弱い?
It tickled me.
くすぐったの
Is it okay to tickle?
くすぐったのダメ?
It might not work.
ダメかもしれない
Which part tickles you the most?
どこが一番くすぐったい?
here?
ここ?
tickles.
くすぐったい
The best part is the armpits.
一番は脇
The closest one?
一番脇?
I told you my weaknesses.
自分の弱点伝えちゃったね
No.
ダメだよ
Where is this?
ここは?
What about here?
ここはどう?
tickles.
くすぐったい
Where is this?
ここは?
good?
いい?
Can I see it?
見ていい?
It's bright so I can see clearly.
明るいからよく見えるわ
It's bright so you can see clearly
明るいからよく見える
circle.
わ
It's embarrassing.
恥 ずかしい
Not really.
わけじゃないよ
Just raise your arms a little.
ちょっと腕を上げるだけ
Hooray?
万歳?
Long live it.
万歳
Wait until I say okay.
いいって言うまでしといて
I haven't touched my armpits.
わき触ってない
It's just my imagination.
気のせい
hang on.
待って
Prepare your heart.
心の準備
Yeah.
うん
Do anything.
何にもして
My face is too big and I get mean.
顔えすぎて意地悪しちゃう
One more time.
もう一回
How long can I endure it?
どこまで耐えれるかな?
Let's start from here.
まずこっからね
It's ticklish though.
わんわんくすぐったいけど
Level 1, here.
レベル1、ここね
Level 2.
レベル2
Suddenly I knew 2 minutes.
急に2分かった
Can I go here?
ここはいける?
Yeah, somehow.
うん、なんとか
Somehow?
なんとか?
I'll be here once.
一回ここでごろーん
Goroon?
ごろーん?
Wow, you look like a model.
すごい、モデルさんみたい
You can go here, right?
ここはいけるでしょ?
That's right, I can do it.
そうそう、いける
Somehow.
なんとか
Well then,
じゃあ、
Are you okay?
大丈夫?
Yeah.
うん
Sorry, I was mean.
ご めんね、意地悪しちゃった
Okay.
いいよ
I'm watching.
見てまーす
Aside.
わき
Yeah.
うん
Don't be embarrassed.
恥ずかしくないように
It hurts so bad.
めちゃくちゃ痛い
Sorry, I was mean.
ごめんごめん、意地悪しちゃった
Has your skin become white again?
また肌白くなった?
Hmm, maybe so.
うーん、そうかも
I don't know.
分かんない
Well then, because I couldn't stand the tickling in my armpits,
じゃあ、 わきのくすぐり耐えられなかったから、
Even if it's a little worn out.
ちょっとバツ着でもね
Open your legs again.
足をもう一気に開いて
feet?
足?
Open more?
もっと開く?
Open more.
もっと開く
It hurts.
痛いよ
close
近
Kuni.
く に
This guy?
こいつ?
All feelings.
全部気持ち
what up?
どうした?
Eh, what?
えー、 なに?
It's embarrassing.
恥ずかしい
It might be embarrassing, but...
恥ずかしいかもしれないけどさ、 ちょっと、
I'm feeling down.
伏しみできてるよ
Is that it?
あれれ?
Why?
どうして?
Oh, he died.
あ、死んだ
Why are you dying?
どうして死んできてるのかな?
Well, I don't know.
えー、分かんない
appear?
見える?
appear.
見える
It looks great, right?
めっちゃ見えるでしょ?
appear.
見える
I was surprised.
びっくりしちゃった
Are you surprised?
びっくりしちゃった?
I was surprised.
びっくりしちゃった
If it was a hand, my hand wouldn't be tickling.
手だったらさ、 手がくすぐってないんだけど、
perhaps.
多分
Hmm, maybe so.
う ーん、そうなのかも
long time no see.
久しぶり
You're pulling it out properly.
ちゃんと抜いてるね
I'm dropping it.
落としてる
落 としてる
That's enough.
もういいよ
Let's go.
いくよ
That's enough.
もういいよ
Let's go.
いくよ
Good.
よいしょ
Dinner?
ごはん?
Hmm.
うーん
No.
ダメ
When you are told no,
ダメって言われると、
Hmm.
う ーん
Hmm, that's embarrassing.
うーん、恥ずかしい
Did you think that?
そっちって思った?
That's right.
そうだ
We went on a date today, and we walked a lot,
今日デートしてさ、いっぱい歩いたからさ、
Are you sweating?
汗かいてるのかな?
Hmm, that's embarrassing.
うーん、恥ずかしい
Well, if that doesn't work, then here.
じゃあ、そこでダメだったらこっちで
Sho.
しょ
Really?
ほ んとに?
ほんとに?
Really.
ほんとに
Show me, show me.
見せて、見せて
Now, let's tweeze your face with both hands.
じゃあ、顔を両手でピンスしよう
It's embarrassing.
恥ずかしい
Does it feel just a little bit better here?
ここちょっとだけ気持ちいいのか?
Don't say things like that.
そういうこと言わないで
I said I wouldn't say it.
言わないって言ったのに
Sorry, I made a mistake.
ごめん、間違った
Well then, let me be honest for the third time again.
じゃあ、もう1回3度目の正直で
Believe me.
信じて
It's embarrassing.
恥ずかしい